[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Is that what they call her -- female president?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "they", "call", "her", "--", "female", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "That's what happened to me, too.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "happened", "to", "me", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Were you disappointed as I was?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "disappointed", "as", "I", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I'm devastated.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "devastated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "ORGAN: Is that how you felt?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Is", "that", "how", "you", "felt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "What'd you rob?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'d", "you", "rob", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Hmm, well, let's see.", "answer_tokens": ["Hmm", ",", "well", ",", "let", "'s", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "I mean, in Hollywood, people come back to life, don't they?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "in", "Hollywood", ",", "people", "come", "back", "to", "life", ",", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "TO", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Was it all that it's cracked up to be, being in bed with a naked Brad Pitt?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "all", "that", "it", "'s", "cracked", "up", "to", "be", ",", "being", "in", "bed", "with", "a", "naked", "Brad", "Pitt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Well -- first of all, who cracked it up to be -- well, anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "who", "cracked", "it", "up", "to", "be", "--", "well", ",", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brad Pitt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Thelma & Louise"]}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Why do you feel so exercised about this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "feel", "so", "exercised", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, from the reaction that women had to \"Thelma & Louise,\" it was an incredible lesson in the power of media images.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "from", "the", "reaction", "that", "women", "had", "to", "``", "Thelma", "&", "Louise", ",", "''", "it", "was", "an", "incredible", "lesson", "in", "the", "power", "of", "media", "images", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", ":", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "What kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well -- so, I have an institute that's now -- a research- based institute.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--", "so", ",", "I", "have", "an", "institute", "that", "'s", "now", "--", "a", "research-", "based", "institute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Is that what you mean?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "The first female president.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "female", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "It's more likely to be one of these tea party candidates because they're the only ones who are currently showing their faces in this particular race?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "more", "likely", "to", "be", "one", "of", "these", "tea", "party", "candidates", "because", "they", "'re", "the", "only", "ones", "who", "are", "currently", "showing", "their", "faces", "in", "this", "particular", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, in this race.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "this", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 156, "question": "It does, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "does", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "You know...", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Is it giving you a little bit of the taste?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "giving", "you", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "the", "taste", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "You know, I liked it very much.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "liked", "it", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "POS", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "That's an advantage, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "an", "advantage", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "I'm not sure that's everyone's reaction.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "that", "'s", "everyone", "'s", "reaction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Where could Hollywood still improve, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "could", "Hollywood", "still", "improve", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "NNP", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, in exactly what I was talking about in reference to kids' movies is have more female characters and have them do more interesting things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "exactly", "what", "I", "was", "talking", "about", "in", "reference", "to", "kids", "'", "movies", "is", "have", "more", "female", "characters", "and", "have", "them", "do", "more", "interesting", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "We're in this together, right?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "in", "this", "together", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "You're not going to say no, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "say", "no", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "You're available?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "available", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "You can start Monday?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "start", "Monday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I'm ready.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "ready", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "That is true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Are you a good girl in real life?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "good", "girl", "in", "real", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I'm a real mix.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "real", "mix", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["late night"]}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "I heard after the Emmy triumph on Sunday, you had a rather late night, Julianna?", "question_tokens": ["I", "heard", "after", "the", "Emmy", "triumph", "on", "Sunday", ",", "you", "had", "a", "rather", "late", "night", ",", "Julianna", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "We had a late night.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "a", "late", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "PERSON": ["Julianna"], "TIME": ["late night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "So, what does it mean to be a good wife?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "what", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "be", "a", "good", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "That's a very good question And they do ask that often and I think it's different for every person.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "question", "And", "they", "do", "ask", "that", "often", "and", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "different", "for", "every", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Did you actually strike the poor man?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "actually", "strike", "the", "poor", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Would you stand by your man?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "stand", "by", "your", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I really think it would depend on the situation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "think", "it", "would", "depend", "on", "the", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What were the memories you had of them splitting up in your life, that you came to the United States with your mother, and how much do you see of your father?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "memories", "you", "had", "of", "them", "splitting", "up", "in", "your", "life", ",", "that", "you", "came", "to", "the", "United", "States", "with", "your", "mother", ",", "and", "how", "much", "do", "you", "see", "of", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, actually, when I was -- when we're very little, my parents split when I was 1 and it was a very amicable split for the most part.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "when", "I", "was", "--", "when", "we", "'re", "very", "little", ",", "my", "parents", "split", "when", "I", "was", "1", "and", "it", "was", "a", "very", "amicable", "split", "for", "the", "most", "part", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Greenstone"]}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Where did you go?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "In East Greenstone (ph), darling.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "East", "Greenstone", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "darling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "You didn't?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "You didn't go to the nightclub at East Greenstone, did you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "go", "to", "the", "nightclub", "at", "East", "Greenstone", ",", "did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "No, I left when I was 13.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "left", "when", "I", "was", "13", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["East Greenstone"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "RB", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "What -- what does that mean exactly?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "what", "does", "that", "mean", "exactly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Well, I think people are going to find out soon enough Sunday night on CBS.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "people", "are", "going", "to", "find", "out", "soon", "enough", "Sunday", "night", "on", "CBS", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Letterman"]}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "``", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Allegations?", "question_tokens": ["Allegations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "No, David Letterman was obsessed with asking what we would see in the first episode and he kept saying, \"Your butt, are we going to see your butt?\"", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "David", "Letterman", "was", "obsessed", "with", "asking", "what", "we", "would", "see", "in", "the", "first", "episode", "and", "he", "kept", "saying", ",", "``", "Your", "butt", ",", "are", "we", "going", "to", "see", "your", "butt", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "No butt at all?", "question_tokens": ["No", "butt", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "You're a Baltimore Ravens fanatic, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "Baltimore", "Ravens", "fanatic", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Baltimore Ravens"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Did you see (INAUDIBLE) last night?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "last", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "NNP", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "...I did...", "answer_tokens": ["...", "I", "did", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "I mean, he took everybody down with it, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "he", "took", "everybody", "down", "with", "it", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I -- I enjoyed it as well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "enjoyed", "it", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Isn't there a drunk Tweeting danger?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "there", "a", "drunk", "Tweeting", "danger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Oh my goodness, I think there's even worse dangers than that.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "my", "goodness", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "even", "worse", "dangers", "than", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "...would be definitely top of the list, I think, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["...", "would", "be", "definitely", "top", "of", "the", "list", ",", "I", "think", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "I mean, are you as pathetically unlucky in love in real life as you are on screen?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "are", "you", "as", "pathetically", "unlucky", "in", "love", "in", "real", "life", "as", "you", "are", "on", "screen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Actually, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "A beautiful girlfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "beautiful", "girlfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "It's like, what's wrong with this guy?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", ",", "what", "'s", "wrong", "with", "this", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "What's wrong with him, I know.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "'s", "wrong", "with", "him", ",", "I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Will Gardner"]}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "But in real life, things are a lot happier?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "real", "life", ",", "things", "are", "a", "lot", "happier", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Things are much better for me than Will Gardner, as far as his emotional life, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Things", "are", "much", "better", "for", "me", "than", "Will", "Gardner", ",", "as", "far", "as", "his", "emotional", "life", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sophie"]}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "And is he comfortable with these steamy love scenes that they're about to unfurl on the nation?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "he", "comfortable", "with", "these", "steamy", "love", "scenes", "that", "they", "'re", "about", "to", "unfurl", "on", "the", "nation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I, you know, my girlfriend Sophie is not only comfortable with it, she wants to see it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", ",", "you", "know", ",", "my", "girlfriend", "Sophie", "is", "not", "only", "comfortable", "with", "it", ",", "she", "wants", "to", "see", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 500, "question": "And your husband, you've banned from watching?", "question_tokens": ["And", "your", "husband", ",", "you", "'ve", "banned", "from", "watching", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "No, I've -- I said to him, I said, I think the first episode, honey, might be steamier than I thought and he said, \"Good, I'll send Sophie flowers.\"", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ve", "--", "I", "said", "to", "him", ",", "I", "said", ",", "I", "think", "the", "first", "episode", ",", "honey", ",", "might", "be", "steamier", "than", "I", "thought", "and", "he", "said", ",", "``", "Good", ",", "I", "'ll", "send", "Sophie", "flowers", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "I'm what?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Alicia.", "answer_tokens": ["Alicia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Why is monogamy not feasible?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "monogamy", "not", "feasible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Well, as a man...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "a", "man", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Arsenal -- Arsenal is playing on Saturday, you said, right?", "question_tokens": ["Arsenal", "--", "Arsenal", "is", "playing", "on", "Saturday", ",", "you", "said", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I don't think it ...you know, our show is based on -- on a lack of monogamy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "...", "you", "know", ",", "our", "show", "is", "based", "on", "--", "on", "a", "lack", "of", "monogamy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", ":", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Do you, like what?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", ",", "like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Like betraying them as -- as -- in friendship or betraying their trust and if we -- if we -- we are so conditioned...", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "betraying", "them", "as", "--", "as", "--", "in", "friendship", "or", "betraying", "their", "trust", "and", "if", "we", "--", "if", "we", "--", "we", "are", "so", "conditioned", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Isn't cheating on them betraying their trust?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "cheating", "on", "them", "betraying", "their", "trust", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Yes, but -- but if you were to think about it this way that, you know, (a) it's a physical thing, it's a desire that we have and we can't, you know, we can -- if you are kind with it then maybe it's going to be OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "--", "but", "if", "you", "were", "to", "think", "about", "it", "this", "way", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "(", "a", ")", "it", "'s", "a", "physical", "thing", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "desire", "that", "we", "have", "and", "we", "ca", "n't", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "can", "--", "if", "you", "are", "kind", "with", "it", "then", "maybe", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Christine?", "question_tokens": ["Christine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I think a big -- big factor is when you have children and you're raising a family, staying together.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "big", "--", "big", "factor", "is", "when", "you", "have", "children", "and", "you", "'re", "raising", "a", "family", ",", "staying", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Do you understand (INAUDIBLE) character?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "NNP", ":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "It feels good because it makes your children happy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "feels", "good", "because", "it", "makes", "your", "children", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Julianna"], "LOCATION": ["Silda"]}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Do you understand why her character, then, would stand by her man?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "why", "her", "character", ",", "then", ",", "would", "stand", "by", "her", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "RB", ",", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "ARANSKI: Yes, in fact, you asked Julianna about the women who stand by their men instead of deserting them and I think a big factor, for instance, Silda, she had two daughters, two daughters of an age to really know what was going on.", "answer_tokens": ["ARANSKI", ":", "Yes", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "you", "asked", "Julianna", "about", "the", "women", "who", "stand", "by", "their", "men", "instead", "of", "deserting", "them", "and", "I", "think", "a", "big", "factor", ",", "for", "instance", ",", "Silda", ",", "she", "had", "two", "daughters", ",", "two", "daughters", "of", "an", "age", "to", "really", "know", "what", "was", "going", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Do you think he's inherently an evil person?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "inherently", "an", "evil", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Wouldn't he, in the end, do anything for political gain?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "he", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "do", "anything", "for", "political", "gain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Yes, but he's still got -- he's still got chink in his armor.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "still", "got", "--", "he", "'s", "still", "got", "chink", "in", "his", "armor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Does he have a moral compass, though?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "have", "a", "moral", "compass", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Yes, it's just kind of slanted a little further.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "kind", "of", "slanted", "a", "little", "further", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "And -- and you get to see a whole different side of him which is really exciting.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "--", "and", "you", "get", "to", "see", "a", "whole", "different", "side", "of", "him", "which", "is", "really", "exciting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Do you (INAUDIBLE), you have got an ex- wife?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "you", "have", "got", "an", "ex-", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "In real life.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "real", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Yes, and in real life you've also recently gone through a civil partnership?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "in", "real", "life", "you", "'ve", "also", "recently", "gone", "through", "a", "civil", "partnership", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "I have a husband.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "husband", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "What would you like to know, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "to", "know", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I don't know, whatever you think I should know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "whatever", "you", "think", "I", "should", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Yes, after -- after you lost, right?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "after", "--", "after", "you", "lost", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "OMFG.", "answer_tokens": ["OMFG", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Are you sure now that you're on the right side of the fence?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "sure", "now", "that", "you", "'re", "on", "the", "right", "side", "of", "the", "fence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "You actually went and saw Magnus at his home, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "actually", "went", "and", "saw", "Magnus", "at", "his", "home", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Magnus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "But he's a remarkable man, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["But", "he", "'s", "a", "remarkable", "man", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "A remarkable man and a beautiful soul.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "remarkable", "man", "and", "a", "beautiful", "soul", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "How about those Bills?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "those", "Bills", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I don't even know what you're talking about.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "even", "know", "what", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Well, they have to come out of the hotel room, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "have", "to", "come", "out", "of", "the", "hotel", "room", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "When do you realize they're at it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "do", "you", "realize", "they", "'re", "at", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "There's a lot of suspicion.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "suspicion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "So, are you confirming, unequivocally, that sex took place?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "are", "you", "confirming", ",", "unequivocally", ",", "that", "sex", "took", "place", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "She's got a new hairdo.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "got", "a", "new", "hairdo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "ARANSKI: Yes, I mean, I think any adult who goes to a hotel where it's $7,800 for the night, I mean, you're not going to sit there for $7,800 and just hold hands?", "question_tokens": ["ARANSKI", ":", "Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "any", "adult", "who", "goes", "to", "a", "hotel", "where", "it", "'s", "$", "7,800", "for", "the", "night", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "sit", "there", "for", "$", "7,800", "and", "just", "hold", "hands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "$", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "$", "CD", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "He's not going to waste that kind of money is my sense, not his character.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "waste", "that", "kind", "of", "money", "is", "my", "sense", ",", "not", "his", "character", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$7,800", "$7,800"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Have you all seen the first episode?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "all", "seen", "the", "first", "episode", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]